I
Voices collide the storm and the flame laughter and chaos it's part of the game
Secrets unravel the stage is alive in psyches arena the strange will survive
afraid let it break from shadows to starlight the truth will be shown the
psyche awakens you're never alone expect the unexpected strange and unusual step
inside the flow the circus of shadows it's psyches show terrible trolls in the
dark take their stand but angels are dancing torchlight and head
Psychies show
Far chow Q
Protected the vibe is tight if you show up wild. You're gone by night tarot cards cut. Don't test the flame get booted fast
We remember your name
guys. I don't know where Psyche is. Was that the hot emo girl he dug up? Was that his sister?
Kind of looks like his sister. If you were a girl, it kind of looks like him.
Anyway, uh, I'm a lot hosting this show. Well, yeah, I did a 13 hour stream. I'm pretty exhausted and
Yeah, I'm still using the primitive aspects of haircare and so forth when you drink when you drink
Kobe's motherfucking
You have rings to your bowels so the firearms you want to try and strain. Yeah, it was uh, it was fine
I got banned off on me twice. I won't say why I
I
Hi
What's up?
Um, it's mostly just straight cis men hitting on her for being a hot like Arab
That's kind of it. You know, that's basically it
If you say the Edward one more time, I'm gonna have to like all right, I'll do my best to not do that, man
I'm gonna fucking lay down
I'll tell you what I treat you like a straight cis man. There you go. Oh
I mean you like you like play around with me a little bit
I did I don't think you I don't think you want me
I think you would want someone really young and like
Thanks Jesus
Well, I could but I mean I fuck women
Have you ever had an experience of the man
If I did I couldn't really talk about it because of my fascist beliefs now, but it was
You might have you did something and like college or something. Well, no, yeah, I
I'll just say that anyway, we won't get into it.
We got shoes on.
I wanna hear it.
No, I wanna hear it.
Did you make it with the drag queen?
Did you do it?
No, the fucking queer you're taking me for.
Did you give your friend a blow job
when you were like hanging out one night?
No, not that either.
You woke up with a gay guy having a bloke.
No, these weird frat fantasies you have
about cis straight breeders,
you need to get this off of your chest.
I'm just saying, but it's not me.
Anyway
Yeah, it's really drunk, but it's fine and like
No
Story tell the game story what happened like what you do with the guy just tell me once I can't I can't do you know
How these people will use this shit again?
Pretend to give it a hypothetical if you were to what would be the story?
If I if I was if I if I what if I was is actually
It's actually, if I was, it would be a cross between like masculine and feminine.
And there would be something but like the problem is you can never produce life with another man with you
Yeah, but I'm a fascist son I can't I can't I can't condone most homosexual behavior
I I'm about the race and about producing more white people so I can't I mean that's that's fine
But it's like what if like, you know, we were just like
from military expedition for like a few days.
Thank you.
Listen, you can.
I
Oh, oh shit, I'm sorry.
Fuck. Hold on.